# **Stan Davis**

Games Programmer

Email: stanley.samson.davis@gmail.com

Portfolio: standavis.dev

# **PROFILE**

I am an enthusiastic and creatively driven programmer with over 3 years experience in games development. This has provided me an extensive knowledge of various languages, and game engines including C++, C#, and Unity. I have a keen interest in building various gameplay systems, and I am constantly learning new skills through personal development.

Feel free to check out my portfolio to see all of my recent projects.

## **SKILLS**

Languages	Game Engines / APIs	Other Skills
C++	Unity	Git
C#	Godot	Collaboration (Slack/JIRA/Teams/Zoom)
Swift / SwiftUI	Unreal	Web (HTML/CSS)
LUA	DirectX	Video Editing (Premiere Pro)
Rust		Music Production / Sound Design (Ableton
		Live / FL Studio)

## **WORK HISTORY**

### Honest Burgers (2021 - Present)

Serving food, drinks, taking payments and providing customer service.

#### The Berkeley - Wetherspoons (2018 - 2019)

Serving drinks, taking payments and customer service.

#### **DotCom Department - Tesco** (2017)

Picking online orders, and customer service.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Games Technology BSc (Hons) (2019 - 2022)

University of the West of England

Grade: **2:1** 

# **BTEC Extended Diploma in Music Technology**

Phone: 07503834590

**Level 3** (2015-2017) Truro College Grade: **DMM** 

## 9 GCSEs (inc. Maths & English) (2012-2015)

Poltair School Grade: **B-C** 

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

Gaming, Game Design, Programming, Music Production, Building Lego